Andrew J. Clement

198 Alpine Dr. Nederland, CO 80466 Tel: (214) 738-5788 Andrew.Clement1@gmail.com

SALES PROFESSIONAL - SaaS Software and Cloud Computing

Top producing sales professional with more than 7 years of experience in providing technical B2B solution sales in the SaaS software and Cloud Computing industries. Highly knowledgeable in a wide variety of SaaS software and Cloud computing solutions, data integration, project management, professional services, social networking and web-based applications. Outstanding team member that is a key contributor to individual and team success.

- Business-to-Business: Cold call and telephone sales expert.
- Prospecting New Clients: Inside and Outside sales experience.
- Build Trust and Respect: Demonstrates expertise & provides exceptional follow-through.
- Lead Qualification & Generation: Understands value of thorough research and positioning.
- Territory Management: Organized and structured planner.
- Excel in Customer Support: Exceptional rapport building ability.
- Superior closing abilities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Regional Account Manager – Portals that transform Office 365/SharePoint into a Digital Workplace 1/2018 - Present SP Marketplace, Penn Valley CA (Startup)

SP Marketplace is for SMB Office 365 users who want to maximize their utilization of Microsoft cloud-based suite. SP Marketplace turns SharePoint from a naked platform to a full Intranet and collaboration structure. Accelerate user adoption and consolidate disparate standalone applications. This next generation business suite built around a Digital Workplace that helps you optimize your business, drive collaboration and improve customer satisfaction whether you are in the office, on the road or at home. SP Marketplace's out-of-box business solutions are "native" to Office 365 and SharePoint.

- Sold and managed government and small to medium businesses accounts: Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, Willis-Knighton Health System, Planet Fitness, Pain Treatment Centers of America, Global Impact, Afton Chemical, and Corbus Pharmaceuticals.
- Sold over \$250,000 in 6 months.
- Created and assisted in marketing campaigns to help grow the business.

World Travel - Solo 1/2017-10/2017

Traveled to Australia, New Zealand, Indonesia, Hong Kong, China, India, Nepal (including Everest Base Camp), Europe.

Enterprise Account Manager - ONESOURCE SaaS Applications Field Sales Thomson Reuters, Carrollton TX

1/2015 - 1/2017

Thomson Reuters provides professionals with the intelligence, technology and human expertise they need to find trusted answers. Enabling professionals in the financial and risk, legal, tax and accounting, and media markets to make the decisions that matter most, all powered by the world's most trusted news organization. Thomson Reuters shares are listed on the Toronto and New York Stock Exchanges (symbol: TRI).

- Sold and managed enterprise accounts: AirBnB, Apple, Bechtel, BKD, LLP, Blue Cross Blue Shield, Cambia Health, Denver Health Medical Plans, Federated Insurance, Health Net, Lyft, Medica, Sanford Health, Sikich, and Toro
- Finished #1 in division at 131% of quota selling over \$750,000 of ONESOURCE SaaS.
- Prospected and sold directly to CFO's, CIO's, Controllers and Senior level management.

Sales Representative - Cloud Applications Inside RealPage, Carrollton Texas

2/2014 - 1/2015

RealPage is a leading provider of comprehensive property management software solutions in the multifamily, commercial, and single-family rental housing industries. RealPage helps apartment management companies and property owners increase efficiency, decrease expenses, enhance the resident experience and generate more revenue. Utilizing its innovative SaaS platform, RealPage software enables easy system integration and streamlines online property management.

- Finished 3rd In Affordable Division.
- First new hire to reach \$250,000 from a class of 60 representatives from all divisions.
- On pace to finish the year at 102% of quota when I exited the company.

Sales Representative - Cloud & On-Premise Software CCH, a Wolters Kluwer business, Dallas Texas

5/2011 - 12/2013

CCH, a Wolters Kluwer business is the leading provider of customer-focused tax, accounting and audit information, software and services for professionals (CCHGroup.com) and is part of the world's largest tax and accounting provider, Wolters Kluwer Tax & Accounting.

- Year 1: Finished #1 in division at 103% of Quota.
- Year 2: Finished #1 in division of 70+ sales representatives at 228% of quota selling on-premise and cloud-based software solutions to CPA firms.
- Quickly establish strong working relationships with clients over the phone and in person.

Freight Broker 1/2011 - 5/2011

Chariot Express, Hurst Texas

Chariot Express is a transportation brokerage company, providing transportation solutions to our customers and carriers. Operating since 1999, Chariot Express is expanding in the DFW and Houston areas.

- Sell transportation brokerage services by developing relationships with potential customers and carriers.
- Contact customers on a daily basis to generate revenue.
- Negotiate lanes and rates from shippers and carriers.
- Monitor shipments during all phases of transport and communicating statuses to the customers.

Sales Specialist - Copiers and Document Management Software Inside Sales Southwest Office Systems/SOS, Dallas Texas

4/2010 - 12/2010

Southwest Office Systems, Inc. founded in 1964 and began as a two-man typewriter repair company. SOS became a SHARP facsimile dealer in 1987, which initiated their entry into digital products. Southwest Office Systems has since grown to be the largest minority-owned, independent office equipment dealer in the Southwest.

- Generate leads: cold call businesses, profile clients, and effectively present and market the Sharp product line to enhance offices' document workflow.
- Network extensively with clients to build successful business-to-business relationships.
- Negotiate terms, write proposals, close sales, setup delivery and write contracts.
- Produced \$50,000 of sales in first 6 months.

EDUCATION

Dale Carnegie Training & Sullivan University

1/2013 - Present

Certificate in IT Management

Hamline University, St. Paul Minnesota

9/2004 - 8/2008

• Business Management